{
	"nacional": {
		"totalPersonas": [{
			"pregunta": "Total de personas de 5 años y más*",
			"respuesta": "total",
			"total": 42326.11,
			"pTotal": 100,
			"Hombres": 20731.68,
			"pHombres": 48.98,
			"Mujeres": 21594.43,
			"pMujeres": 51.02
		}],
		"soporteImpreso": [{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"respuesta": "S� leyó",
				"total": 34714.64,
				"pTotal": 82.02,
				"Hombres": 16707.1,
				"pHombres": 80.59,
				"Mujeres": 18007.53,
				"pMujeres": 83.39
			},
			{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"respuesta": "No leyó",
				"total": 7611.48,
				"pTotal": 17.98,
				"Hombres": 4024.58,
				"pHombres": 19.41,
				"Mujeres": 3586.9,
				"pMujeres": 16.61
			}
		],
		"soporteDigital": [{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"respuesta": "S� leyó",
				"total": 29793.5,
				"pTotal": 70.39,
				"Hombres": 14527.72,
				"pHombres": 70.08,
				"Mujeres": 15265.78,
				"pMujeres": 70.69
			},
			{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"respuesta": "No leyó",
				"total": 12532.61,
				"pTotal": 29.61,
				"Hombres": 6203.96,
				"pHombres": 29.93,
				"Mujeres": 6328.65,
				"pMujeres": 29.31
			}
		]
	},
	"cabeceras": {
		"totalPersonas": [{
			"pregunta": "Total de personas de 5 años y mas*",
			"respuesta": "total",
			"total": 33456,
			"pTotal": 100,
			"Hombres": 16096,
			"pHombres": 48.1,
			"Mujeres": 17360,
			"pMujeres": 51.9
		}],
		"soporteImpreso": [{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"total": 27968,
				"pTotal": 83.6,
				"Hombres": 13304,
				"pHombres": 82.7,
				"Mujeres": 14664,
				"pMujeres": 84.5
			},
			{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"respuesta": "No leyo",
				"total": 5488,
				"pTotal": 16.4,
				"Hombres": 2792,
				"pHombres": 17.3,
				"Mujeres": 2696,
				"pMujeres": 15.5
			}
		],
		"soporteDigital": [{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"total": 24996,
				"pTotal": 74.7,
				"Hombres": 12019,
				"pHombres": 74.7,
				"Mujeres": 12977,
				"pMujeres": 74.8
			},
			{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"respuesta": "No leyo",
				"total": 8460,
				"pTotal": 25.3,
				"Hombres": 4077,
				"pHombres": 25.3,
				"Mujeres": 4383,
				"pMujeres": 25.2
			}
		]
	},
	"centrosPoblados": {
		"totalPersonas": [{
			"pregunta": "Total de personas de 5 años y mas*",
			"respuesta": "total",
			"total": 8870,
			"pTotal": 100,
			"Hombres": 4636,
			"pHombres": 52.3,
			"Mujeres": 4234,
			"pMujeres": 47.7
		}],
		"soporteImpreso": [{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"total": 6747,
				"pTotal": 76.1,
				"Hombres": 3403,
				"pHombres": 73.4,
				"Mujeres": 3343,
				"pMujeres": 79
			},
			{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte impreso",
				"respuesta": "No leyo",
				"total": 2123,
				"pTotal": 23.9,
				"Hombres": 1232,
				"pHombres": 26.6,
				"Mujeres": 891,
				"pMujeres": 21
			}
		],
		"soporteDigital": [{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"respuesta": "Si leyo",
				"total": 4798,
				"pTotal": 54.1,
				"Hombres": 2509,
				"pHombres": 54.1,
				"Mujeres": 2289,
				"pMujeres": 54.1
			},
			{
				"pregunta": "Material en soporte digital",
				"respuesta": "No leyo",
				"total": 4072,
				"pTotal": 45.9,
				"Hombres": 2127,
				"pHombres": 45.9,
				"Mujeres": 1945,
				"pMujeres": 45.9
			}
		]
	}
}